Guide to the Sigur Center for Asian Studies records, 1992-1998 RG0028
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Sigur Center for Asian Studies records
1992-1998
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Sigur Center for Asian Studies
RG0028
10.5 Linear Feet
Collection includes conference reports, project files, financial records and correspondence.
Restrictions on Access
Some records may be restricted.
Acquisition Information
Materials acquired through transfers from Sigur Center for Asian Studies.
Historical or Biographical Note
The Sigur Center sponsors research projects, study groups, conferences, and lectures on political, social, economic, and security issues in Asia. It also hosts the Visiting Scholar and Visiting Research Associate Programs, bringing eminent scholars and top policy planners from universities and government organizations around the world to the Elliott School to teach and pursue their own research.
Collection Scope and Content
Materials in this collection include conference reports, project files (Asia Pacific Trade Policy project, the 24th Sino-American Conference, and the Singapore Conference, etc), financial records and correspondence. The material covers the years 1992-1998.
Conferences; Finance; Washington (D.C.); George Washington University; Gaston Sigur Center for Asian Studies
- FINANCIAL RU03412, 1992 -1993 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- FINANCIAL RU03111-Detail Reports, 1992 -1993 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- FINANCIAL RU03414-East Asia Studies Program, 1992 -1993 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- FINANCIAL PAYROLL FOLDER, 1992 -1993 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- FINANCIAL PAYROLL-#1, 1992 -1993 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- FINANCIAL PAYROLL-#2, 1992 -1993 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- FINANCIAL LEILA HERTZBERG-PAYROLL, 1992 -1993 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- FINANCIAL RU03111-STARTUP EXPENSES, 1993 -1994 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- FINANCIAL RU03412/53311, 1993 -1994 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- FINANCIAL RU03412/53411, 1993 -1994 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- FINANCIAL RU03412/54111, 1993 -1994 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- FINANCIAL RU03412/55121, 1993 -1994 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- FINANCIAL RU03412/55511, 1993 -1994 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- FINANCIAL RU03412/59501, 1993 -1994 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- FINANCIAL RU03412/59508, 1993 -1994 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- FINANCIAL RU03414/43114, 1993 -1994 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- FINANCIAL RU03414/47571, 1993 -1994 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- FINANCIAL RU03414/52612, 1993 -1994 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- FINANCIAL RU03414/53311, 1993 -1994 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- FINANCIAL RU03414/53411, 1993 -1994 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- FINANCIAL RU03414/54111, 1993 -1994 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- FINANCIAL RU03414/59509, 1993 -1994 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- FINANCIAL RU03414/54141, 1993 -1994 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- FINANCIAL OFFICE EXPENSES, 1993 -1994 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Conference 2/5/95 Prof. Ni Xiaoquan, 02/05/1995 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Conference "2/15/95 Kim, Lilley, Oberdorfer", 02/15/1995 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Conference 2/24/95 Prof. 02/24/Pyo, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Conference 5/4/95 Japanese LDP Members, 05/04/1995 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Conference 2/20/96 Prof. Kim Kyong-Dong, 02/20/1996 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Conference 5/4/95 Amb. Watanabe, 05/04/1995 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Conference 10/16/95 Distinguished Visiting Lecturer Series, 10/16/1995 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Conference 9/12/95 Hiroshi Kimura Lecture, 09/12/1995 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Conference 10/7/93 Kim Dae-Jung Luncheon Lecture, 10/07/1993 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Conference 4/30/96 Luncheon for Japanese Delegation, 04/30/1996 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Conference "10/11/97, 4/97 Trilateral Conference", 10/11/1997 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Conference "9/10, 6/95 Trilateral Security Conference", 06/1995 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Conference "5/6, 12/96 Trilater Symposium", 12/1996 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Conference "17/18, 6/96 Trilateral Symposium", 06/1996 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Conference "17/18, 6/98 Trilateral Symposium 2", 06/1998 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Conference 1/3/8/94 Uruguay Seminar, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Conference "26/28, 1/96 Asia-Pacific Trade Policy-Roundtable Meeting", 1996 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Financial R UO7412/55121, 1993 -1994 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Financial R UO7412/58533, 1993 -1994 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Financial R UO7412/55121, 1993 -1994 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Financial R UO7412/54111, 1993 -1994 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Financial R UO3111-Start Up/ Seawash, 1993 -1994 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Financial JF Revenues, 1993 -1994 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Financial JF Transfers, 1993 -1994 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Financial JF Salary Payments, 1993 -1994 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Financial J. Pollack Articles, 1993 -1994 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Financial Chicago Council on Foreign Relations, 1993 -1994 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Financial Local Events, 1993 -1994 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Financial "Abridged Bio, Politics of China", 1993 -1994 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Financial Trilateral Budget, 1993 -1994 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Financial "Trilateral Project, YR 2 Working File", 1993 -1994 (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Financial Trilateral Symposium- Financials, 1993 -1994 (Box 2, Folder 32)
- Financial Trilateral Research project, 1993 -1994 (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Financial Dr. Kim's San Francisco Trip, 1993 -1994 (Box 2, Folder 34)
- Financial AHN Papers, 1993 -1994 (Box 2, Folder 35)
- Financial Grant Papers, 1993 -1994 (Box 2, Folder 36)
- Financial Canadian Grant Info, 1993 -1994 (Box 2, Folder 37)
- Financial Japan Foundation Grants, 1993 -1994 (Box 2, Folder 38)
- Financial US Japan Foundation, 1993 -1994 (Box 2, Folder 39)
- Financial Start up/Office Expenses, 1993 -1994 (Box 2, Folder 40)
- Financial RU, 1993 -1994 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Financial 3414/53411, 1993 -1994 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Financial 3414/54111, 1993 -1994 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Financial 3414/52612, 1993 -1994 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Financial 3141/52612, 1993 -1994 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Financial 3414 East Asian Studies Program, 1993 -1994 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Financial 3414/44211, 1993 -1994 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Financial 3414/47571, 1993 -1994 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Financial 7411 SC National Cheng Chi Univ., 1993 -1994 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Financial 3111 Ledger, 1993 -1994 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Financial 3111 Budget, 1993 -1994 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Financial 3412 Budget, 1993 -1994 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Financial 3412Ledger, 1993 -1994 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Financial 3414 Ledger, 1993 -1994 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Financial 3414 Budget, 1993 -1994 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Financial 3412/51225, 1993 -1994 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Financial 3412/53411, 1993 -1994 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Financial 3412/54111, 1993 -1994 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Financial 3412/55511, 1993 -1994 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Financial 3412/59508, 1993 -1994 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Financial 7411/52612, 1993 -1994 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Financial 7411 Sigur Center, 1993 -1994 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Financial 7411/53311, 1993 -1994 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Financial 7411/53411, 1993 -1994 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Financial 7411/54111, 1993 -1994 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Financial 7411/55121, 1993 -1994 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Financial 7411/55121, 1993 -1994 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Financial 7411/43114, 1993 -1994 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Financial 7411/44211, 1993 -1994 (Box 3, Folder 29)
- Financial 7411/47571, 1993 -1994 (Box 3, Folder 30)
- Financial 7411/5111, 1993 -1994 (Box 3, Folder 31)
- Financial 7411/51123, 1993 -1994 (Box 3, Folder 32)
- Financial 7411/51226, 1993 -1994 (Box 3, Folder 33)
- Financial 7411/52221, 1993 -1994 (Box 3, Folder 34)
- Financial 3414/55121, 1993 -1994 (Box 3, Folder 35)
- Financial 3414/55331, 1993 -1994 (Box 3, Folder 36)
- Financial 3414/55511, 1993 -1994 (Box 3, Folder 37)
- Financial 3414/55561, 1993 -1994 (Box 3, Folder 38)
- Financial 3414/57115, 1993 -1994 (Box 3, Folder 39)
- Financial 3414/58952, 1993 -1994 (Box 3, Folder 40)
- Financial 3414/59501, 1993 -1994 (Box 3, Folder 41)
- Financial 3414/59508, 1993 -1994 (Box 3, Folder 42)
- Financial 7411/55511, 1993 -1994 (Box 3, Folder 43)
- Financial 7411/55561, 1993 -1994 (Box 3, Folder 44)
- Financial 7411/57115, 1993 -1994 (Box 3, Folder 45)
- Financial 7411/58952, 1993 -1994 (Box 3, Folder 46)
- Financial 7411/59501, 1993 -1994 (Box 3, Folder 47)
- Financial 7411/59508, 1993 -1994 (Box 3, Folder 48)
- Financial 7412/43114, 1993 -1994 (Box 3, Folder 49)
- Financial 3414/57115, 1993 -1994 (Box 3, Folder 50)
- Financial 3414/58952, 1993 -1994 (Box 3, Folder 51)
- Financial 3414/59508, 1993 -1994 (Box 3, Folder 52)
- Financial 7411, 1993 -1994 (Box 3, Folder 53)
- Financial 43114 Revenues, 1993 -1994 (Box 3, Folder 54)
- Financial 7411/51123, 1993 -1994 (Box 3, Folder 55)
- Financial 7411/52691, 1993 -1994 (Box 3, Folder 56)
- Financial 7411/53111, 1993 -1994 (Box 3, Folder 57)
- Financial 7411/53111, 1993 -1994 (Box 3, Folder 58)
- Financial 7411/53311, 1993 -1994 (Box 3, Folder 59)
- Financial 7411/53411, 1993 -1994 (Box 3, Folder 60)
- Financial 55511 Non GW Print/ Repro, 1993 -1994 (Box 3, Folder 61)
- Financial 7411/59508, 1993 -1994 (Box 3, Folder 62)
- Financial 7412/52691, 1993 -1994 (Box 3, Folder 63)
- Financial 7412/53112, 1993 -1994 (Box 3, Folder 64)
- Financial 7412/58533, 1993 -1994 (Box 3, Folder 65)
- Financial 7412/59508, 1993 -1994 (Box 3, Folder 66)
- Financial 7412/59111, 1993 -1994 (Box 3, Folder 67)
- Financial 7412/59501, 1993 -1994 (Box 3, Folder 68)
- Financial 7412/59509, 1993 -1994 (Box 3, Folder 69)
- Financial 7412/53411, 1993 -1994 (Box 3, Folder 70)
- Financial 7412/53311, 1993 -1994 (Box 3, Folder 71)
- Financial 7412/53411, 1993 -1994 (Box 3, Folder 72)
- Financial 7412/54111, 1993 -1994 (Box 3, Folder 73)
- Financial 7412/55121, 1993 -1994 (Box 3, Folder 74)
- Financial 7411/54111, 1993 -1994 (Box 3, Folder 75)
- Financial 7411/55121, 1993 -1994 (Box 3, Folder 76)
- Financial 57115 Student Stipends, 1993 -1994 (Box 3, Folder 77)
- Financial 7411/59509, 1993 -1994 (Box 3, Folder 78)
- Financial 7412/53111, 1993 -1994 (Box 3, Folder 79)
- Financial 7412/55511, 1993 -1994 (Box 3, Folder 80)
- Financial 7412/57111, 1993 -1994 (Box 3, Folder 81)
- Financial 7412/44211, 1993 -1994 (Box 3, Folder 82)
- Financial 7412/47571, 1993 -1994 (Box 3, Folder 83)
- Financial 7412/51123, 1993 -1994 (Box 3, Folder 84)
- Financial 7412/52131, 1993 -1994 (Box 3, Folder 85)
- Financial 7412/52221, 1993 -1994 (Box 3, Folder 86)
- Financial 7412/53112, 1993 -1994 (Box 3, Folder 87)
- Financial 7412/53411, 1993 -1994 (Box 3, Folder 88)
- Financial 7412/54111, 1993 -1994 (Box 3, Folder 89)
- Financial 7412/55121, 1993 -1994 (Box 3, Folder 90)
- Financial 7412/57111, 1993 -1994 (Box 3, Folder 91)
- Financial 7412/53111, 1993 -1994 (Box 3, Folder 92)
- Financial 7412/57115, 1993 -1994 (Box 3, Folder 93)
- Financial 7412/58533, 1993 -1994 (Box 3, Folder 94)
- Financial 7412/58522, 1993 -1994 (Box 3, Folder 95)
- Financial 7412/58952, 1993 -1994 (Box 3, Folder 96)
- Financial 7412/59111, 1993 -1994 (Box 3, Folder 97)
- Financial 7412/59501, 1993 -1994 (Box 3, Folder 98)
- Financial 7412/59504, 1993 -1994 (Box 3, Folder 99)
- Financial 7412/59501, 1993 -1994 (Box 3, Folder 100)
- Financial 7412/59508, 1993 -1994 (Box 3, Folder 101)
- Financial 7412/910842, 1993 -1994 (Box 3, Folder 102)
- Financial 3414/51123, 1993 -1994 (Box 3, Folder 103)
- Conferences Taiwan Study Group, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Conferences Papers, 1994 -1995 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Conferences Papers, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Conferences Papers, 1980 -1992 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Conferences Taiwan Study Group, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Conferences Old Conferences, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Conferences Planning TRI, undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Conferences Twiwant Study Missions, undated (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Conferences Touchbase for Windows, undated (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Conferences Welling Lecture Series, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Conferences "Chron, W. White", 1995 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Conferences Correspondence, undated (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Conferences RUO 3111 Sigur Center Start-Up Funds, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Project/Office Development of ROC on Taiwan, 1993 -1995 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Project/Office Visiting Scholars Info, 1993 -1995 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Project/Office Trilateral-Year Three, 1993 -1995 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Project/Office Yomuri Conference Files, 1993 -1995 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Project/Office Nippon Foundation Annual Meeting, 1993 -1995 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Project/Office "America, China, and Japan, Deliberation Program", 1993 -1995 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Project/Office Working Paper-US and Japanese Trade Policies, 1993 -1995 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Project/Office Prof. Kim- Poli Sci Classes, 1993 -1995 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Project/Office Working Paper-response to Japanese Technology, 1993 -1995 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Project/Office Trilateral-Year Three, 1993 -1995 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Project/Office Research Associate- PN Marcus, 1993 -1995 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Project/Office Asia Pacific Trade Policy Project, 1993 -1995 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Project/Office Asia Pacific Trade Policy Project 2, 1993 -1995 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Project/Office Budget Projection, 1993 -1995 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Project/Office Budget Projection 2, 1993 -1995 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Project/Office Us Japan Foundation, 1993 -1995 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Project/Office Us Japan Grant Transactions, 1993 -1995 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Project/Office Follow Up File, 1993 -1995 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Project/Office JNAS Complimentary Mailing, 1993 -1995 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Project/Office General Japan Fund, 1993 -1995 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Project/Office General Taiwan Fund, 1993 -1995 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Project/Office TRI, 1993 -1995 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Project/Office TPP, 1993 -1995 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Project/Office Dr. Johnson/Kim Tracel, 1993 -1995 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Project/Office Corp. AmEx card and related receipts, 1993 -1995 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- Project/Office Domestic Waybill Receipts, 1993 -1995 (Box 5, Folder 26)
- Project/Office International Waybill Receipts, 1993 -1995 (Box 5, Folder 27)
- Project/Office Trilateral-Year Three, 1993 -1995 (Box 5, Folder 28)
- Project/Office Research Associate- W. Kansteiner, 1993 -1995 (Box 5, Folder 29)
- Project/Office Senior Research Assoc. DR EDK Melby, 1993 -1995 (Box 5, Folder 30)
- Project/Office Earhart Foundation, 1993 -1995 (Box 5, Folder 31)
- Project/Office GE Fund Grant, 1993 -1995 (Box 5, Folder 32)
- Project/Office Donner, 1993 -1995 (Box 5, Folder 33)
- Project/Office APEC, 1993 -1995 (Box 5, Folder 34)
- Project/Office GE Fund Grant, 1993 -1995 (Box 5, Folder 35)
- Project/Office Donner Canadian Foundation Grant, 1993 -1995 (Box 5, Folder 36)
- Project/Office RUO7412/52612, 1994 -1995 (Box 5, Folder 37)
- Project/Office Accounting, 1993 -1995 (Box 5, Folder 38)
- Project/Office RUO7412/52612 Contd., 1993 -1995 (Box 5, Folder 39)
- Project/Office Hugh Corbet, 1993 -1995 (Box 5, Folder 40)
- Project/Office Senior research Assoc. H. Corbet, 1993 -1995 (Box 5, Folder 41)
- Project/Office TPP, 1993 -1995 (Box 5, Folder 42)
- Conference/Project Asia Pacific Trade Policy Project, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Conference/Project Asia Pacific Trade Policy Project IV, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Conference/Project Asia Pacific Trade Policy Project II, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Conference/Project Asia Pacific Trade Policy Project III, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Conference/Project Asia Pacific Trade Meeting, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Conference/Project Yomiuri Shimbun Conference, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Conference/Project Taiwan Conference, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Conference/Project Korea Conference, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Conference/Project Conference on the US and Asia, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Conference/Project 24th Sino-American Conference, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Conference/Project Singapore Conference, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Office Correspondence: WR Johnson, 1994 -1995 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Office Correspondence: YC Kim and General Chron, 1994 -1996 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Office "General Chron, papers and Handouts", undated (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Office Correspondence: YC Kim and General Chron, 1994 -1995 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Office Budget Summary 3413 3111, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Office Important File W. White, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Office Sigur File/Chron, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 7)